it's barcelona paris saint-germain
the last 16 of the little competition
called the champions league
absolutely
incredible atmosphere in the stadium
rafinha will play it into the
[Applause]
up
unable to clear it there was a flick
back by luis suarez
[Applause]
messi strikes it oh
not too far
over the crossbar there anymore just
upside the bounty box on the far side
and that is what you need to do as well
the elaborate one twos into the box
flings it inside to a niece who lets him
run for sweating sweating looking to
play it over towards iniesta iniesta
wins the ball back eel
oh
[Applause]
time
waiting for the
whistle there it is
messi steps up hits you into the net
and it's a cracker of a penalty
ambassador
now psg go forward the ball
is off the post
and then
go defensive as the long ball forward
falls to the spot oh it's a goal
it's a goal for cavani
has made the run he's not upside down he
commanding oh what a save by stegen
tremendous saving messi messi inside
there he shoots um
just wide
let's see what neymar can do here neymar
hits it oh what a goal what a goal by
neymar what a beautiful free kick
[Applause]
[Music]
the players urging the ball forward into
the box louis swelling is brought down
it's a penalty it's a penalty it's a
penalty oh my dear me dear me dear me
neymar steps up
is it the net
nemo
has made him five one
he's made it 5-1
they're going for that ball now um teddy
will play him into the box pk on the
other
ball collected by 12
and he gave could this be the time ball
played into the box and it went towards
test again ball cleared but it'll be a
chance to play it in again neymar on the
ball though gets onto his left foot and
plays into the box
he's in the right he see the knight he's
in the net he's in the net he's in the
net he's in the net
barcelona have
one
six
barcelona have won
and they're in the next round of the
champions league
6-1 this
is history
this has not
been done before
and i don't know if we'll ever see it
ever again
but this is the kind of victory that not
only
gets you to the next round
and i tell you what what a beautiful
ball headed away by machole there's the
final whistle
there's the final whistle
barcelona
six
harry sanja man
one
bossa
and in the next round of the champions
league
i love this job
[Applause]